Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - E-H
        - Fascinating Force - Doin' the bang, 1989; SR-24732; Fascinating Force (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24733. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # FMS 62347; A-side Matrix # FMS-62347A
          Select Record
        - Fascinating Force - Doin' the bang, 1989; SR-24733; Fascinating Force (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24732. 2 copies. Promo
        - Fascinating Force - Stupid; We are the ones, 1988; SR-24734; Fascinating Force (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24735. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # FMS 62313; A-side Matrix # FMS-62313-SIDE1
        - Fascinating Force - Stupid; We are the ones, 1988; SR-24735; Fascinating Force (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24734. 2 copies. Promo
        - Fascination - Still miss you, 1994; SR-24736; Fascination (Box 31)
          Catalog # CR-318-DJ; A-side Matrix # CR-318A
          Cutting Records
        - Fashion - Love shadow, 1982; SR-24737; Fashion (Box 31)
          Catalog # SP 145; A-side Matrix # SP-145-SA
          Arista
        - Fast - Leather boys from the Asphalt Jungle, 1981; SR-24738; Fast (Box 31)
          Catalog # RR2001; A-side Matrix # K13179 RR2001-ONE
          Recca Records
        - Fatboy Slim - Punk to funk, 1996; SR-24739; Fatboy Slim (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24740. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SKINT 12; A-side Matrix # SKINT-12-A
          Skint
        - Fatboy Slim - Punk to funk, 1996; SR-24740; Fatboy Slim (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24739. 2 copies.
        - Fatboy Slim - Better living through chemistry (disc one), 1996; SR-24741; Fatboy Slim (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24742. Double album.
          Catalog # BRASSIC 2LP; A-side Matrix # BRASSIC 2 LP-A1
        - Fatboy Slim - Better living through chemistry (disc two), 1996; SR-24742; Fatboy Slim (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24741. Double album.
          Catalog # BRASSIC 2LP; A-side Matrix # BRASSIC 2 LP-C1
        - Fatboy Slim - Santa Cruz, 1995; SR-24743; Fatboy Slim (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24744. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SKINT 1; A-side Matrix # 12-SKINT-1-A
        - Fatboy Slim - Santa Cruz, 1995; SR-24744; Fatboy Slim (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24743. 2 copies.
        - Fat Boys - Coming back hard again, 1988; SR-24745; Fat Boys (Box 31)
          Catalog # 422 835 809-1; A-side Matrix # 422-835-809-1-AS-SP
          Tin Pan Apple
        - Fat Larry's Band - Off the wall, 1977; SR-24746; Fat Larry's Band (Box 31)
          Catalog # STX-4103; A-side Matrix # STX-4103-A-1
          Stax
          Berkeley, California
        - Fatback - So delicious, 1985; SR-24747; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 31)
          Catalog # 90253-1; A-side Matrix # STCTN 855625A 1-1
        - Fatback - Fired up 'n' kickin', 1978; SR-24748; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24749. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # SP-1-6718; A-side Matrix # T1 SP-1-6718 AS-CT
          Spring Records
        - Fatback - Fired up 'n' kickin', 1978; SR-24749; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24748. 2 copies. Promo
        - Fatback - With love, 1983; SR-24750; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 31)
          Catalog # SPR-33-6741; A-side Matrix # SPR-336741-A
        - Fatback - With love, 1983; SR-24751; Fatback; Fatback Band (Box 31)
        - Father Father - We are all so very happy, 1991; SR-24752; Father Father (Box 31)
          Catalog # 828 258-1; A-side Matrix # 828 258 1 S1-1 670 07 113
          Go! Discs
        - Father's Children - Father's children, 1979; SR-24753; Father's Children (Box 31)
          Catalog # SRM-1-3755; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-3755-PR-A4-RE
        - Fats Comet & The Big Sound - Bop bop, 1984; SR-24754; Fats Comet & The Big Sound (Box 31)
          Catalog # WR 001; A-side Matrix # WR 001 A2
          World Records
        - Fatty - Princer; Ice Cream; Bad Luck; Spinning Around, SR-24755; Fatty (Box 31)
          Catalog # FOP001; A-side Matrix # FOP001 A
          Trutone
          South Africa
        - Faye, Alma - Doin' it, 1979; SR-24756; Faye, Alma (Box 31)
          Catalog # NBLP 7143 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7143-AS
        - Faze-O - Good thang, 1978; SR-24757; Faze-O (Box 31)
          Catalog # SH 741; A-side Matrix # ST-SH-784119-A
          She Records
        - Faze-O - Breakin' the funk, 1979; SR-24758; Faze-O (Box 31)
          Catalog # SH 742; A-side Matrix # STSH 794275 A
        - Faze-O - Breakin' the funk, 1979; SR-24759; Faze-O (Box 31)
        - FDR - FDR, 1987; SR-24760; FDR (Box 31)
          Catalog # F-9652; A-side Matrix # F-9652 A1
          Fantasy
        - Fela Ransome-Kuti - Fela's London scene, 1983; SR-24761; Fela Ransome-Kuti; Africa 70 (Box 31)
          Catalog # M 2399; A-side Matrix # M-2399-A
          Editions Makossa
        - Fela Anikulapo Kuti - Up side down, 1976; SR-24762; Fela Anikulapo Kuti; Africa 70 (Box 31)
          Catalog # SP 44290; A-side Matrix # XZAL-15125-1
          London Records
        - Fẹla Ransome Kuti - Open & close, 1981; SR-24763; Fẹla Ransome Kuti; Africa 70 (Box 31)
          Catalog # 2C 068-81.957; A-side Matrix # 81957 A 21 M6 335449 2
          EMI
        - Felder, Wilton - Inherit the wind, 1980; SR-24764; Felder, Wilton (Box 31)
          Catalog # MCA-5144; A-side Matrix # MCA 2080-AM1
        - Felder, Wilton - We all have a star, 1978; SR-24765; Felder, Wilton (Box 31)
          Catalog # AA-1109; A-side Matrix # AA 1109 A SM1
          ABC Records
        - Felix & Jarvis - Felix & Jarvis, 1983; SR-24766; Felix & Jarvis (Box 31)
          Catalog # QUS 1006; A-side Matrix # QUS 1006 A
          Quality
          Scarborough, Ontario
        - Ferguson, Jay - White noise, 1982; SR-24767; Ferguson, Jay (Box 31)
          Catalog # ST-12196; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12196 F10
        - Ferguson, Maynard - Theme from "Battlestar Galactica", 1978; SR-24768; Ferguson, Maynard (Box 31)
          Catalog # ASD 509; A-side Matrix # XSS-164920-1A
        - Fernandez, Pamela - You don't own me, 1990; SR-24769; Fernandez, Pamela (Box 31)
          Catalog # LM-401; A-side Matrix # LM-401-AA
          Lumar Music
          United States
        - Fever - Beat of the night; Pump it up, 1979; SR-24770; Fever (Box 31)
          Catalog # D-143; A-side Matrix # D-143A
        - Fever - The one tonight; Dreams and desire, 1980; SR-24771; Fever (Box 31)
          Catalog # D-158; A-side Matrix # D 158A RE1-1B S1
        - Fever - Dreams and desire, 1980; SR-24772; Fever (Box 31)
          Catalog # F-9595; A-side Matrix # F9595 A RE1
        - FF Yellowhand - You want every night; Can you feel it, 1981; SR-24773; FF Yellowhand (Box 31)
          Catalog # FST-1453; A-side Matrix # FST-1453-A
          Fire-Sign Limited
        - Fiasco, Johnny - Hardgrooves vol. I, 1996; SR-24774; Fiasco, Johnny (Box 31)
          Catalog # STR-007; A-side Matrix # STR-007-A
          5XO-294
        - Fields, Lee - Problems, 2002; SR-24775; Fields, Lee (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24776. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SFLP004; A-side Matrix # SFCP-004-A
          Soul Fire
        - Fields, Lee - Problems, 2002; SR-24776; Fields, Lee (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24775. 2 copies.
        - Final Approach - We like to boogie, 1976; SR-24777; Final Approach (Box 31)
          Catalog # GPD-2; A-side Matrix # A-GPD-2-2 1-1
          Gold Plate Records
          Buffalo, New York
        - Final Edition - Betcha can't love just one (can't keep running away), 1980; SR-24778; Final Edition (Box 31)
          Catalog # VAR-19811; A-side Matrix # VAR-19811-A
          VAP Records, Inc.
          Amityville, New York
        - Fine Quality - Ahh dance, 1981; SR-24779; Fine Quality; Cuz (Box 31)
          Catalog # SH-563; A-side Matrix # VID-211-A
          Sugar Hill Records
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - Finesse & Synquis - Soul sisters, 1988; SR-24780; Finesse & Synquis (Box 31)
          Catalog # MCA-42177; A-side Matrix # MCA 7797 FW1
        - Fingers Inc. - Another side (disc one), 1988; SR-24781; Fingers Inc. (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24782. Double album.
          Catalog # FING 1; A-side Matrix # DM C-1208 A-1/2-88
          Jack Trax
        - Fingers Inc. - Another side (disc two), 1988; SR-24782; Fingers Inc. (Box 31)
          In same jacket as # SR-24781. Double album.
          Catalog # FING 1; A-side Matrix # DM C-1209 A-1/2-88
        - Finished Touch - Need to know you better, 1978; SR-24783; Finished Touch (Box 31)
          Catalog # M7-906R1; A-side Matrix # M7-906R1A-18B
          Motown
        - Finley, Karen - The truth is hard to swallow, 1987; SR-24784; Finley, Karen (Box 31)
          Catalog # PWAI 069; A-side Matrix # POW-WOW-A-1 PW-A1-069-A
          Pow Wow Art International
        - Finley, Karen - Tales of taboo, 1986; SR-24785; Finley, Karen (Box 31)
          Catalog # PWAI 049; A-side Matrix # PWAI-049-A
        - First Choice - Hold your horses, 1979; SR-24786; First Choice (Box 32)
          Catalog # GA 9502; A-side Matrix # GA-9502-A 1
          Gold Mind Records
        - First Choice - Breakaway, 1980; SR-24787; First Choice (Box 32)
          Catalog # GA 9505; A-side Matrix # GA-9505-A 1
        - First Choice - Love thang, 1979; SR-24788; First Choice (Box 32)
          Catalog # GG 502; A-side Matrix # GG-502A GOL FWCS K-10823
          Salsoul Records
        - Five Special - Do it Baby; It's a wonderful day, 1979; SR-24789; Five Special (Box 32)
          Catalog # AS-11439; A-side Matrix # ASS-11439 A-SP 1-1
        - FK1000 - White stripped, 2003; SR-24790; FK1000 (Box 32)
          Catalog # KINKY 002; A-side Matrix # 7591-FK1000-1 (A) S-52790
          Kinky
        - Flack, Roberta - Bustin' loose (music from the Original Motion Picture soundtrack), 1981; SR-24791; Flack, Roberta (Box 32)
          Catalog # MCA-5141; A-side Matrix # MCA-2382
        - Flack, Roberta - Live & more (disc one), 1980; SR-24792; Flack, Roberta; Bryson, Peabo (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24793. Double album.
          Catalog # SD 2-7004; A-side Matrix # STA-804599-B
        - Flack, Roberta - Live & more (disc two), 1980; SR-24793; Flack, Roberta; Bryson, Peabo (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24792. Double album.
          Catalog # SD 2-7004; A-side Matrix # STA-804601-B
        - Flack, Roberta - Roberta Flack featuring Donny Hathaway, 1979; SR-24794; Flack, Roberta; Hathaway, Donny (Box 32)
          Catalog # SD 16013; A-side Matrix # STA-794429-A
        - Flack, Roberta - Back together again, 1979; SR-24795; Flack, Roberta; Hathaway, Donny (Box 32)
          Catalog # DMD 232; A-side Matrix # ST-DM 38413-1
        - Fleetwood Mac - Tango in the night, 1987; SR-24796; Fleetwood Mac (Box 32)
          Catalog # 9 25471-1; A-side Matrix # 1-25471-A-SR1-DMM SP3-1
          Warner Bros. Records
        - Fleetwood, Mick - You weren't in love, SR-24797; Fleetwood, Mick (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24798. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # DJL1-4106; A-side Matrix # DJL1-4106A-1
        - Fleetwood, Mick - You weren't in love, SR-24798; Fleetwood, Mick (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24797. 2 copies. Promo
        - Fleetwood, Mick - The Visitor, 1981; SR-24799; Fleetwood, Mick (Box 32)
          Catalog # AFL1-4080; A-side Matrix # AFL1-4080A
        - Fleming, Garfield - Don't send me away; You got dat right, 1981; SR-24800; Fleming, Garfield (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24801. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # BKD 505; A-side Matrix # B-KD-505A
          Becket Records
        - Fleming, Garfield - Don't send me away; You got dat right, 1981; SR-24801; Fleming, Garfield (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24800. 2 copies. Promo
        - Flesh-N-Bone - T.H.U.G.S. Trues Humbly United Gatherin' Souls (disc one), 1996; SR-24802; Flesh-N-Bone (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24803
          Catalog # 314 533 539-1; A-side Matrix # VINYL-1 B14-533-954-1 A
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Flesh-N-Bone - T.H.U.G.S. Trues Humbly United Gatherin' Souls (disc two), 1996; SR-24803; Flesh-N-Bone (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24802
          Catalog # 314 533 539-1; A-side Matrix # 2-314-533-955-1A
        - Flip Da Scrip - You to me, 1996; SR-24804; Flip Da Scrip (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24805. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # NTR 004; A-side Matrix # NTR-004-A1
          Nightown Records
          Krefeld, Germany
        - Flip Da Scrip - You to me, 1996; SR-24805; Flip Da Scrip (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24804. 2 copies. Promo
        - Flip Da Scrip - You to me, 1996; SR-24806; Flip Da Scrip (Box 32)
        - Flip Da Scrip - Throw ya hands in the air '95, 1995; SR-24807; Flip Da Scrip (Box 32)
          Catalog # NTR 001; A-side Matrix # NTR-001-A1
        - Flip Da Scrip - Throw ya hands in the air '95, 1995; SR-24808; Flip Da Scrip (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24809. 2 copies. Promo
        - Flip Da Scrip - Throw ya hands in the air '95, 1995; SR-24809; Flip Da Scrip (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24808. 2 copies. Promo
        - Flirts - Boy crazy; Jukebox (don't put another dime in that), 1982; SR-24810; Flirts (Box 32)
          Catalog # OR 719; A-side Matrix # OR-719-A A-1
          "O" Records
        - Floaters - Magic, 1978; SR-24811; Floaters (Box 32)
          Catalog # AA-1047; A-side Matrix # AA-1047-A
        - Floaters - Float into the future, 1979; SR-24812; Floaters (Box 32)
          Catalog # MCA-3093; A-side Matrix # MCA-1747 CR-1
        - Focus - Live At The Rainbow, 1973; SR-24813; Focus (Box 32)
          Catalog # SAS-7408; A-side Matrix # SAS-7408-A-1
        - Fog City Productions - Bulldog Breaks volume one, 1991; SR-24814; Fog City Productions (Box 32)
          Catalog # BD-001; A-side Matrix # BDLP-001 A1 L-43136
          Fog City Records
        - Folino - Secret, SR-24815; Folino (Box 32)
          Catalog # XR 001; A-side Matrix # 0008X05 ABC001A
          Xotic Records
        - Force 10 - Force 10, 1981; SR-24816; Force 10 (Box 32)
          Catalog # BSK 3557; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3557 S2 B-15831-S2
        - Force MD's - Touch and go, 1987; SR-24817; Force MD's (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24818. Different discs.
          Catalog # TBLP 25631; A-side Matrix # TBLP 25631-A-SH1 17130 B-28067-SH1
        - Force MD's - Touch and go, 1987; SR-24818; Force MD's (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24817. Different discs.
          Catalog # TB 905; A-side Matrix # TB-905-A
        - Force MD's - Touch and go, 1987; SR-24819; Force MD's (Box 32)
        - Force MD's - Chillin', 1985; SR-24820; Force MD's (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24821. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TBLP 1010; A-side Matrix # TBLP-1010-A
        - Force MD's - Chillin', 1985; SR-24821; Force MD's (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24820. 2 copies.
        - Foreign Legion - Kidnapper Van: beats to rock while bike stealin' (disc one), 2000; SR-24822; Foreign Legion (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24823. Double album.
          Catalog # IUR 9001-1; A-side Matrix # INSURB 9001-1 A S-43097
          Insiduous Urban Records
        - Foreign Legion - Kidnapper Van: beats to rock while bike stealin' (disc two), 2000; SR-24823; Foreign Legion (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24822. Double album.
          Catalog # IUR 9001-1; A-side Matrix # INSURB 9001-1 C DC BQS S-43099
        - Foreigner - 4, 1981; SR-24824; Foreigner (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24825. 2 copies.
          Catalog # XSD 16999; A-side Matrix # XSD-16999-A
        - Foreigner - 4, 1981; SR-24825; Foreigner (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24824. 2 copies.
        - Foreigner - Foreigner, 1977; SR-24826; Foreigner (Box 32)
          Catalog # SD 19109; A-side Matrix # ST-A-773809-A
        - Foremost Poets - Facing the impossible, 1998; SR-24827; Foremost Poets (Box 32)
          Catalog # SOW-423; A-side Matrix # SOW-423 A
          Soundmen On Wax
        - Foremost Poets - The Spy-Chiatrist, 1998; SR-24828; Foremost Poets (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24829. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SOW-424; A-side Matrix # SOW-424 A
        - Foremost Poets - The Spy-Chiatrist, 1998; SR-24829; Foremost Poets (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24828. 2 copies.
        - Formula V - Killer groove, 1984; SR-24830; Formula V (Box 32)
          Catalog # MAL 1213; A-side Matrix # MAL 1213A
          Malaco Records
          Jackson, Mississippi
        - Fort Knox Five - Dodge City Rockers, 2003; SR-24831; Fort Knox Five (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24832. Different discs.
          Catalog # FKX-001; A-side Matrix # FKX-001-A
          Fort Knox Recordings
        - Fort Knox Five - The big score, 2003; SR-24832; Fort Knox Five (Box 32)
          In same jacket as # SR-24831. Different discs.
          Catalog # FKX-002; A-side Matrix # FKX-002-1A
        - Forte, John - Ninety nine (flash the message), 1998; SR-24833; Forte, John (Box 32)
          Catalog # 44 78770; A-side Matrix # XSS78770A-1A
          Ruffhouse Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Foster, Ronnie - Cheshire Cat, 1975; SR-24834; Foster, Ronnie (Box 32)
          Catalog # BN-LA425-G; A-side Matrix # BNLA 425-1
          Blue Note
        - Foster, Ronnie - Delight, 1979; SR-24835; Foster, Ronnie (Box 33)
          Catalog # JC 36019; A-side Matrix # PAL-36019-1D
        - Foster, Sylvi - Hookey, 1982; SR-24836; Foster, Sylvi (Box 33)
          Catalog # MIX 107; A-side Matrix # M 107V
          Discomagic Records
          Milano, Italy
        - Four Tops - Tonight!, 1981; SR-24837; Four Tops (Box 33)
          Catalog # NBLP 7258; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7258-AS-PW
        - Four Tops - Live & in concert, 1974; SR-24838; Four Tops (Box 33)
          Catalog # DSD-50188; A-side Matrix # DSD-50188-A
          ABC/Dunhill Records
        - Fox, Neal - A painting, 1977; SR-24839; Fox, Neal (Box 33)
          Catalog # APL1-2190; A-side Matrix # APL1-2190-A-5
        - Foxy - Hot number; Call it love; Give me a break, 1979; SR-24840; Foxy (Box 33)
          Catalog # 131; A-side Matrix # TKD-131-R2-A
          T.K. Disco
          Hialeah, Florida
        - Foxy - Get off; Tena's song, 1976; SR-24841; Foxy (Box 33)
          Catalog # 88; A-side Matrix # TKD-88-A
        - Foxy - Get off; Tena's song, 1976; SR-24842; Foxy (Box 33)
        - Frampton, Peter - Breaking all the rules, 1981; SR-24843; Frampton, Peter (Box 33)
          Catalog # SP-3722; A-side Matrix # SP-03722-A-CP1
        - Franco - Ekaba-Kaba (Yo Moko Okabeli Ngai Ye Oh), 1987; SR-24844; Franco; T.P. O.K. Jazz (Box 33)
          Catalog # 9508; A-side Matrix # AM 9508 A
        - Frank Chickens - Fujiyama Mama; Shellfish bamboo; We are Ninja, 1984; SR-24845; Frank Chickens (Box 33)
          Catalog # KAZ 10 T; A-side Matrix # KAZ-10(T)A
          Kaz Records
        - Franke & The Knockouts - Franke & The Knockouts, 1981; SR-24846; Franke & The Knockouts (Box 33)
          Catalog # BXL1-7755; A-side Matrix # BXL-1-7755-A
          Millennium
        - Franklin, Aretha - Who's zoomin' who?, 1985; SR-24847; Franklin, Aretha (Box 33)
          Catalog # AL 8-8286; A-side Matrix # AL 8 8286 SA RE1-2
        - Franklin, Aretha - Aretha's gold, 1969; SR-24848; Franklin, Aretha (Box 33)
          Catalog # SD 8227; A-side Matrix # ST-A-691567-C
        - Franklin, Aretha - Love all the hurt away, 1981; SR-24849; Franklin, Aretha (Box 33)
          Catalog # AL 9552; A-side Matrix # AL-9552-SA-TV1
        - Franklin, Aretha - The best of Aretha Franklin - Queen of Soul, 1982; SR-24850; Franklin, Aretha (Box 33)
          Catalog # AN 8131; A-side Matrix # AN8131-A1150467-1-1
          Arrival Records
        - Franklin, Aretha - Almighty Fire, 1978; SR-24851; Franklin, Aretha (Box 33)
          Catalog # SD 19161; A-side Matrix # ST-A-773999-A
        - Franklin, Aretha - Amazing grace (disc one), 1972; SR-24852; Franklin, Aretha (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24853. Double album.
          Catalog # SD 2-906; A-side Matrix # ST-A-722493-F
        - Franklin, Aretha - Amazing grace (disc two), 1972; SR-24853; Franklin, Aretha (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24852. Double album.
          Catalog # SD 2-906; A-side Matrix # ST-A-722495C
        - Franklin, Rodney - Endless flight, 1981; SR-24854; Franklin, Rodney (Box 33)
          Catalog # FC 37154; A-side Matrix # AL 37154-1B
        - Frantique - Frantique, 1979; SR-24855; Frantique (Box 33)
          Catalog # JZ 36026; A-side Matrix # PIR-1A-AL36026
          Philadelphia International Records
        - Fraser, Dean - Big Up!, 1997; SR-24856; Fraser, Dean (Box 33)
          Catalog # IJLP 4003; A-side Matrix # IJLP 4003 A1
          Island Jamaica Jazz ‎
        - Free Expression - Save the last dance for me; Chill-Out!, 1980; SR-24857; Free Expression (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24858. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SPV 39; A-side Matrix # SPV 39 A-1D
          Vanguard Disco
          Santa Monica, California
        - Free Expression - Save the last dance for me; Chill-Out!, 1980; SR-24858; Free Expression (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24857. 2 copies.
        - Free Life - Free Life, 1978; SR-24859; Free Life (Box 33)
          Catalog # JE 35392; A-side Matrix # PAL 35392-1D
        - Freedom - Changes of time, 1981; SR-24860; Freedom (Box 33)
          Catalog # MAL 7403; A-side Matrix # MAL-7403-A RE-3-1
        - Freedom - Changes of time, 1981; SR-24861; Freedom (Box 33)
        - Freeez - Southern Freeez, 1981; SR-24862; Freeez (Box 33)
          Catalog # BEG 51T; A-side Matrix # BEG 51 T A1
          Beggars Banquet
        - Freestylers - Up rock E.P., 1997; SR-24863; Freestylers (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24864. Different discs.
          Catalog # FNT2; A-side Matrix # FNT 2 A1
          Freskanova
          Pangbourne, Berkshire
        - Freestylers - Adventures in Freestyle EP, 1997; SR-24864; Freestylers (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24863. Different discs.
          Catalog # FNT7; A-side Matrix # FNT-7-A1
        - Freestylers - Ruffneck, 1998; SR-24865; Freestylers (Box 33)
          Catalog # FNT12; A-side Matrix # FNT-12-A3
        - Freestylers - Pressure point (disc one), 2001; SR-24866; Freestylers (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24867; SR-24868. Triple album.
          Catalog # FNTLP6; A-side Matrix # FNTLP6-1A
        - Freestylers - Pressure point (disc two), 2001; SR-24867; Freestylers (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24866; SR-24868. Triple album.
          Catalog # FNTLP6; A-side Matrix # FNTLP6 2A1
        - Freestylers - Pressure point (disc three), 2001; SR-24868; Freestylers (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24866; SR-24867. Triple album.
          Catalog # FNTLP6; A-side Matrix # FNTLP 6-3 A2
        - Freestylers - Here we go, 1999; SR-24869; Freestylers (Box 33)
          Catalog # FNT19; A-side Matrix # FNT 19-A1
        - Fresh, Doug E. - The show; La-Di-Da-Di, 1985; SR-24870; Fresh, Doug E.; Doug E. Fresh And The Get Fresh Crew; M. C. Ricky D (Box 33)
          Catalog # D-242; A-side Matrix # D-242-A-1
          Reality
          Jersey City, New Jersey
        - Frick And Frack - You shouldn't have done it; Jealous girls, 1986; SR-24871; Frick And Frack (Box 33)
          Catalog # RM 1003-12C-A-I; A-side Matrix # RM1003A
          Romil
          Cambria Heights, Queens